Washington Area Performing Arts Video Archives (WAPAVA)
DC Public Library Special Collections
- Series 1
  - Collaborators - Spooky Action Theatre, 2016-02-28 - 2016-02-28 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - District Merchants - Folger Theatre, 2016-06-15 - 2016-06-15 (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Fantasticks - Rep Stage, 2014-05-18 - 2014-05-18 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Floyd Collins - 1st Stage, 2016-06-25 - 2016-06-25 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Our Town - Faction of Fools Theatre Company, 2015-06-20 - 2016-06-25 (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Sense and Sensibility - Folger Theatre, 2016-09-27 - 2016-09-27 (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Taming of the Shrew - Shakespeare Theatre Company, 2016-05-26 - 2016-06-25 (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - The Critic / Real Inspector Hound - Shakespeare Theatre Company, 2015-10-23 - 2015-10-23 (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Twelve Angry Men - American Century Theater, 2015-08-08 - 2015-08-08 (Box 106, Folder 11)
  - When January Feels Like Summer - Mosaic Theater Company of DC, 2016-06-11 - 2016-06-25 (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - 32nd Annual Helen Hayes Awards - theatreWashington, 2016-05-23 - 2016-05-23 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - A Christmas Carol - A Ghost Story of Christmas - Ford's Theatre, 2014-12-13 - 2014-12-13 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - A Lesson from Aloes - Quotidian Theatre Company, 2016-05-21 - 2016-05-21 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Black Nativity - Theatre Alliance, 2015-12-14 - 2015-12-14 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Colossal - Olney Theatre Center, 2014-09-27 - 2014-09-27 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - Driving Miss Daisy - Ford's Theatre, 2014-10-04 - 2014-10-04 (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Intelligent Homosexual's Guide to Capitalism and Socialism with a Key to the Scriptures - Theatre J, 2014-12-20 - 2014-12-20 (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Las Meninas - Rep Stage, 2011-05-03 - 2011-05-03 (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - Little Dancer - Kennedy Center, 2014-11-25 - 2014-11-25 (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Me Nobody Knows - University of Maryland, 2013-03-09 - 2013-03-09 (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - Occupied Territories - Theatre Alliance, 2015-06-29 - 2015-06-29 (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - Seven Guitars - No Rules Theatre Company, 2014-09-27 - 2014-09-27 (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - Shining City - SCENA Theatre, 2014-09-19 - 2014-09-19 (Box 107, Folder 13)
  - Tempest - Shakespeare Theatre Company, 2014-12-13 - 2014-12-13 (Box 107, Folder 14)
  - Travels with my Aunt - Rep Stage, 2010-09-09 - 2010-09-09 (Box 107, Folder 15)
  - Wittenberg - Rep Stage, 2009-09-10 - 2009-09-10 (Box 107, Folder 16)
  - As You Like It - Shakespeare Theatre Company, 2014-11-22 - 2014-11-22 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Back to Methuselah - Washington Stage Guild, 2014-03-22 - 2014-03-22 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - For Colored Girls - Theatre Alliance, 2016-03-20 - 2016-03-20 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Guard - Ford's Theatre, 2015-10-03 - 2015-10-03 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Intimate Apparel - University of Maryland, 2015-10-17 - 2015-10-17 (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Ironbound - Round House Theatre, 2015-09-29 - 2015-09-29 (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Tartuffe - Shakespeare Theatre Company, 2015-06-19 - 2015-06-19 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Twelfth Night - Shakespeare Theatre Company, 2008-12-13 - 2008-12-13 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Word Become Flesh - Theatre Alliance, 2016-03-20 - 2016-03-20 (Box 108, Folder 9)